

# DURGA PANDA

W E B D E V E L O P E R D A T A A N A L Y S T

9535426798

durgaprasadpan@gmail.com

Bangalore, India

durgapanda@github.io/portfolio

## TECH SKILLS

- Front End (HTML, CSS, JS, Angular)
- Back End (NodeJs, ExpressJs)
- Database (MongoDB, MySQL)
- CMS (Strapi)
- BI Tools (Power BI)
- Cloud (AWS Certified)
- Microsoft Power Platform
- UI (Photoshop)
- Prototyping tools (Figma, Adobe XD)

## SOFT SKILLS

- Project Management
- · People management
- Stakeholder management
- Effective Communication
- Analytical Thinking

# EDUCATION

**BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY** 

JNTU Hyderabad 2006 - 2010

### PROFILE

A motivated professional web developer and data analyst with 12 years of industry expertise in web development, data analysis and project management. A strategic and agile thinker known for driving change by tackling ambiguous problems and effectively communicating solutions.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### LEAD WEB DEVELOPER & DATA ANALYST

Fidelity Investments

2019 - Present

- Manage a team of Full stack developers. As a team we are responsible for end to end webapp development and deployment.
- Responsible for stakeholder management, core responsibilities include interacting with the stakeholders to determine project scope and project timelines, and work with the team to effective manage the project without any overspill.
- As a Data Analyst, core responsibilities include interact with the stakeholders to understand the data and the dashboard requirements and develop several Power BI dashboards using Microsoft Power BI

#### WEB DEVELOPER

Fidelity Investments

2011 - 2019

- Developed several web applications using Angular and front end technologies. Created Rest APIs using NodeJs and ExpressJs
- Developed front-end responsive web pages with HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript.
- Designed web pages and applications that met business and user goals increased user satisfaction by an average of 20%.